<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <modNameReadable>Soft Warm Beds</modNameReadable>
    <modIdentifier>JPT_SoftWarmBeds</modIdentifier>
    <!--<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1713295858</linkUrl>-->
    <linkUrl>https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs</linkUrl>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SoftWarmBeds_1_0_6</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.6</assemblyVersion>
    <content>Check out the new options panel (Options > Mod Settings), where you can customize the beds' color scheme to your liking!|Also, notice the beddings' category has been changed to &lt;i&gt;Apparel&lt;/i&gt;, for compatibility purposes.|The full change log is on our Steam Workshop page.</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SoftWarmBeds_2_0_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>2.0.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Your beds have just been improved!&lt;/b&gt;|- The code for the bed insulation properties has been revised to overcome a RimWorld quirk. Now it will also affect your pawn's "Slept in Cold/Heat" thoughts, just like it was supposed to.|- You can now copy &amp; paste beddings settings from one bed to another.|- &lt;i&gt;Hospitality&lt;/i&gt; is no longer required!|- Improved performance &amp; compatibility with other mods.|You can find the full change log on our Steam Workshop page.|(NOTE: Due to the changes, loading a saved game for the first time with the development mode activated might produce some red errors on the log window. They are harmless, please just ignore them.)</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="SoftWarmBeds.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SoftWarmBeds_2_5</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>2.5</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;A new feature was added to the mod settings!&lt;/b&gt;
      |img:MiyuriMode|caption:You can now choose to have your beds manually unmade by a colonist, instead of the bedding just popping out when you command it to unmake. It works just like other game objects with and on/off switch. 

To activate this, open the mod settings panel (Options > Mod Settings) and select &lt;i&gt;Require a colonist to unmake beds&lt;/i&gt;.
      |Other improvements on this version:
      |- The rest effectiveness for the Animal Bed was adjusted so it doesn't get too powerful once the textile softness bonus is applied.
      |- The report window for a sleeping pawn takes the bed into account for the min/max comfortable temperature calculation once again (it was missing on RW 1.1).
      |
      |img:Quarantine|caption:The new settings feature was a request by one of our earliest supporters on our Ko-fi page. However small, the fact he decided to turn his appreciation into a material contribution meant a lot to me back then. Having this level of support is what fuels mod development! Now, because of the COVID-19 lockdown, those contributions became even more important. So I've put up this one-time campaign as an incentive for those who are able to help me get through this period.
      |&lt;b&gt;I have three brand new mods that are ready to go&lt;/b&gt;, and I'll release them as donations reach their goals. If only a fraction of &lt;i&gt;Soft Warm Beds&lt;/i&gt; subscribers decide to take action, these mods will be out before we know it!
      |Follow the link above or go to https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs to contribute &amp; check more details.
      |You can contact me anytime, on Ko-Fi or on Steam. Many, many thanks for your support!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>  
  
</Defs>